[
  {
    "substring": "an",
    "answers": [
      "BD",
      "BA",
      "BT",
      "BW",
      "RW",
      "TM",
      "TJ",
      "RO",
      "GS",
      "GS",
      "JP",
      "GY",
      "GF",
      "GL",
      "GH",
      "OM",
      "JO",
      "HM",
      "SJ",
      "SJ",
      "PA",
      "PK",
      "PL",
      "UZ",
      "MM",
      "MR",
      "IM",
      "UG",
      "TZ",
      "TZ",
      "FR",
      "FI",
      "FK",
      "NL",
      "VU",
      "NZ",
      "CH",
      "CA",
      "CF",
      "SZ",
      "KG",
      "SS",
      "KN",
      "ST",
      "SM",
      "KZ",
      "KY",
      "SD",
      "DO",
      "DE",
      "LB",
      "TW",
      "TT",
      "LK",
      "LT",
      "TH",
      "VA",
      "VC",
      "AD",
      "AG",
      "AG",
      "AF",
      "AF",
      "IS",
      "IR",
      "AL",
      "AO",
      "AQ",
      "AX",
      "AZ",
      "IE"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'an'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ia",
    "answers": [
      "BG",
      "BA",
      "BO",
      "RU",
      "RS",
      "RO",
      "GS",
      "GQ",
      "GF",
      "GE",
      "GM",
      "TN",
      "HR",
      "PF",
      "ZM",
      "EE",
      "ET",
      "SO",
      "SA",
      "MN",
      "MK",
      "MR",
      "TZ",
      "MY",
      "FM",
      "NA",
      "NC",
      "NG",
      "CO",
      "SY",
      "KH",
      "SK",
      "SI",
      "DZ",
      "LC",
      "LV",
      "LT",
      "LR",
      "AM",
      "AL",
      "AU",
      "AT",
      "IN",
      "ID"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ia'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "in",
    "answers": [
      "BF",
      "BA",
      "BH",
      "BJ",
      "GW",
      "GQ",
      "GB",
      "GN",
      "PS",
      "PG",
      "PH",
      "ES",
      "MF",
      "MF",
      "SH",
      "FI",
      "CN",
      "SR",
      "KN",
      "ST",
      "SM",
      "SG",
      "DO",
      "DM",
      "VG",
      "LC",
      "TT",
      "LI",
      "VC",
      "VC",
      "VC",
      "VI",
      "AR",
      "IN",
      "ID",
      "UA"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'in'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nd",
    "answers": [
      "BA",
      "BI",
      "RW",
      "GS",
      "GS",
      "GL",
      "HN",
      "HM",
      "SJ",
      "PL",
      "UG",
      "FI",
      "FK",
      "NL",
      "NZ",
      "CH",
      "SZ",
      "KN",
      "ST",
      "TT",
      "TH",
      "VC",
      "AD",
      "AG",
      "IS",
      "IN",
      "AX",
      "IE",
      "ID"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nd'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "al",
    "answers": [
      "GT",
      "GQ",
      "SV",
      "GI",
      "HM",
      "PS",
      "PW",
      "PT",
      "SJ",
      "IT",
      "SO",
      "ML",
      "MH",
      "MT",
      "MW",
      "MV",
      "MY",
      "FK",
      "NC",
      "NZ",
      "NP",
      "CF",
      "SN",
      "DZ",
      "TV",
      "AL",
      "AU",
      "AX"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'al'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ma",
    "answers": [
      "JM",
      "BS",
      "RO",
      "GT",
      "OM",
      "SJ",
      "PA",
      "SO",
      "MG",
      "MF",
      "MM",
      "ML",
      "MO",
      "MH",
      "MK",
      "MU",
      "MT",
      "MW",
      "MV",
      "MR",
      "IM",
      "MY",
      "SM",
      "KY",
      "DK",
      "DE",
      "YT"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ma'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ar",
    "answers": [
      "BG",
      "BB",
      "BY",
      "GI",
      "HU",
      "HM",
      "SJ",
      "PY",
      "EH",
      "SA",
      "MG",
      "MF",
      "MM",
      "MH",
      "FO",
      "NI",
      "SM",
      "DK",
      "AE",
      "AG",
      "AM",
      "AQ",
      "AR",
      "AW",
      "QA"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ar'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ni",
    "answers": [
      "BA",
      "BJ",
      "RE",
      "TM",
      "RO",
      "GB",
      "TN",
      "EE",
      "MK",
      "MR",
      "TZ",
      "NI",
      "NC",
      "NE",
      "NG",
      "SI",
      "DO",
      "DM",
      "US",
      "TT",
      "LT",
      "AE",
      "AF",
      "AM",
      "AL"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ni'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "la",
    "answers": [
      "BD",
      "BY",
      "TK",
      "GT",
      "GL",
      "VE",
      "PW",
      "PL",
      "MW",
      "MY",
      "FI",
      "FK",
      "NL",
      "NZ",
      "CH",
      "SZ",
      "LA",
      "LK",
      "LV",
      "TH",
      "IS",
      "AO",
      "AX",
      "IE"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'la'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ne",
    "answers": [
      "BN",
      "GW",
      "GQ",
      "GN",
      "VE",
      "PS",
      "PF",
      "PG",
      "PG",
      "PH",
      "ME",
      "FM",
      "NL",
      "NC",
      "NZ",
      "NP",
      "KN",
      "SN",
      "SL",
      "VC",
      "ID",
      "UA"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ne'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "en",
    "answers": [
      "BJ",
      "TM",
      "GF",
      "GD",
      "GL",
      "VE",
      "SJ",
      "PF",
      "ME",
      "SH",
      "CF",
      "KE",
      "SI",
      "SN",
      "SE",
      "DK",
      "YE",
      "LI",
      "VC",
      "VC",
      "AM",
      "AR"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'en'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ri",
    "answers": [
      "BG",
      "GQ",
      "PR",
      "ZA",
      "ER",
      "MU",
      "MR",
      "NG",
      "CF",
      "CR",
      "SY",
      "SR",
      "KI",
      "ST",
      "SM",
      "VG",
      "DZ",
      "TT",
      "LK",
      "LR",
      "AT"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ri'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "on",
    "answers": [
      "RE",
      "GA",
      "HK",
      "HK",
      "HN",
      "HM",
      "EE",
      "SB",
      "ME",
      "MC",
      "MN",
      "MK",
      "FM",
      "NC",
      "CM",
      "CG",
      "CD",
      "SL",
      "LB",
      "TO",
      "ID"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'on'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "er",
    "answers": [
      "BA",
      "BM",
      "JE",
      "RS",
      "GG",
      "PR",
      "PE",
      "EH",
      "ER",
      "NL",
      "NE",
      "NG",
      "CH",
      "CM",
      "CV",
      "SL",
      "DE",
      "DZ",
      "LR",
      "AZ"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'er'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ra",
    "answers": [
      "BH",
      "BR",
      "GI",
      "HN",
      "PY",
      "IQ",
      "EH",
      "SA",
      "IL",
      "FR",
      "NI",
      "CF",
      "CD",
      "SL",
      "AE",
      "AE",
      "AD",
      "IR",
      "AU",
      "UA"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ra'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ic",
    "answers": [
      "JM",
      "GS",
      "PR",
      "ZA",
      "MX",
      "FM",
      "NI",
      "CG",
      "CF",
      "CF",
      "CD",
      "CD",
      "CZ",
      "CR",
      "DO",
      "DO",
      "DM",
      "VA",
      "IS",
      "AQ"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ic'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "na",
    "answers": [
      "BF",
      "BA",
      "BW",
      "GY",
      "GF",
      "GD",
      "GH",
      "HM",
      "PA",
      "VN",
      "MC",
      "SH",
      "NA",
      "NR",
      "CN",
      "CA",
      "SR",
      "VC",
      "AR"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'na'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ta",
    "answers": [
      "BT",
      "TM",
      "TJ",
      "TJ",
      "GI",
      "PK",
      "IT",
      "UZ",
      "MT",
      "MR",
      "TZ",
      "CR",
      "KG",
      "KZ",
      "US",
      "TW",
      "AF",
      "AQ",
      "QA"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ta'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ca",
    "answers": [
      "JM",
      "PN",
      "ZA",
      "MG",
      "MO",
      "NI",
      "NC",
      "CM",
      "CA",
      "CF",
      "CR",
      "CV",
      "KH",
      "KY",
      "DO",
      "DM",
      "VA",
      "AQ"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ca'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "or",
    "answers": [
      "TL",
      "GS",
      "GQ",
      "GE",
      "SV",
      "JO",
      "PT",
      "EC",
      "MA",
      "NO",
      "NF",
      "CI",
      "KM",
      "KR",
      "KP",
      "KP",
      "SG",
      "AD"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'or'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "st",
    "answers": [
      "TL",
      "TM",
      "TJ",
      "PS",
      "PK",
      "EH",
      "EE",
      "UZ",
      "CI",
      "CR",
      "KG",
      "KZ",
      "US",
      "LI",
      "AF",
      "AU",
      "AT"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'st'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "re",
    "answers": [
      "RE",
      "GR",
      "GF",
      "GD",
      "GL",
      "PF",
      "ER",
      "CG",
      "CF",
      "CD",
      "CZ",
      "KR",
      "KP",
      "SG",
      "DO",
      "VC",
      "IE"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 're'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "li",
    "answers": [
      "BO",
      "BZ",
      "PH",
      "SO",
      "ML",
      "MN",
      "CG",
      "CF",
      "CD",
      "CZ",
      "DO",
      "LI",
      "LT",
      "LR",
      "LY",
      "AU"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'li'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ba",
    "answers": [
      "BD",
      "BB",
      "BB",
      "BH",
      "BS",
      "SJ",
      "ZW",
      "CU",
      "KI",
      "LB",
      "TT",
      "AG",
      "AL",
      "AW",
      "AZ"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ba'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ai",
    "answers": [
      "BH",
      "JM",
      "HT",
      "PN",
      "ES",
      "MF",
      "SH",
      "KN",
      "KW",
      "LC",
      "TW",
      "TH",
      "VC",
      "AZ",
      "UA"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ai'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "th",
    "answers": [
      "GS",
      "GS",
      "GS",
      "ZA",
      "ET",
      "NL",
      "CG",
      "CD",
      "SS",
      "KR",
      "KP",
      "LT",
      "LS",
      "TH",
      "VC"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'th'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "es",
    "answers": [
      "BD",
      "PS",
      "PF",
      "PH",
      "EH",
      "EE",
      "MV",
      "FM",
      "SC",
      "US",
      "LS",
      "VC",
      "AE",
      "ID"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'es'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ti",
    "answers": [
      "TL",
      "HR",
      "HT",
      "PS",
      "MF",
      "MU",
      "CD",
      "KI",
      "DJ",
      "VG",
      "VA",
      "AG",
      "AQ",
      "AR"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ti'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "gu",
    "answers": [
      "GW",
      "GU",
      "GT",
      "GQ",
      "GP",
      "GY",
      "GG",
      "GF",
      "GN",
      "PY",
      "PG",
      "NI",
      "UY",
      "AG"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'gu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "it",
    "answers": [
      "GB",
      "HT",
      "PN",
      "IT",
      "ER",
      "MU",
      "MR",
      "CH",
      "KN",
      "KW",
      "VG",
      "US",
      "LT",
      "AE"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'it'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "am",
    "answers": [
      "JM",
      "WS",
      "BS",
      "GU",
      "GM",
      "PA",
      "ZM",
      "VN",
      "NA",
      "CM",
      "SR",
      "KH",
      "MZ"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'am'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sa",
    "answers": [
      "WS",
      "GW",
      "GS",
      "SV",
      "EH",
      "SA",
      "MF",
      "SH",
      "KN",
      "ST",
      "SM",
      "LC",
      "VC"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "el",
    "answers": [
      "BE",
      "BY",
      "BZ",
      "TK",
      "GP",
      "SV",
      "VE",
      "IL",
      "SH",
      "SC",
      "IS",
      "IE"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'el'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "do",
    "answers": [
      "BB",
      "GB",
      "SV",
      "HM",
      "EC",
      "MD",
      "MK",
      "NC",
      "DO",
      "DM",
      "AD",
      "ID"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'do'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ua",
    "answers": [
      "GU",
      "GT",
      "GQ",
      "GP",
      "PY",
      "PG",
      "EC",
      "NI",
      "VU",
      "UY",
      "LT",
      "AG"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ua'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ng",
    "answers": [
      "BD",
      "GB",
      "HU",
      "HK",
      "HK",
      "MN",
      "CG",
      "CD",
      "SG",
      "TO",
      "AO"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ng'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ad",
    "answers": [
      "BD",
      "BB",
      "GP",
      "GD",
      "SV",
      "EC",
      "MG",
      "CA",
      "TT",
      "TD",
      "VC"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ad'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ur",
    "answers": [
      "BF",
      "BI",
      "TM",
      "HN",
      "MU",
      "MR",
      "NR",
      "SR",
      "UY",
      "TR",
      "LU"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ur'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "da",
    "answers": [
      "BM",
      "RW",
      "GD",
      "JO",
      "MG",
      "UG",
      "CA",
      "SS",
      "SD",
      "TT",
      "AG"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'da'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "mo",
    "answers": [
      "WS",
      "TL",
      "SB",
      "ME",
      "MD",
      "MA",
      "MC",
      "MN",
      "CD",
      "KM",
      "MZ"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'mo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "is",
    "answers": [
      "TM",
      "TJ",
      "GW",
      "TN",
      "PK",
      "UZ",
      "IM",
      "IL",
      "KN",
      "VG",
      "AF"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'is'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "at",
    "answers": [
      "GT",
      "GQ",
      "HR",
      "VU",
      "CD",
      "KI",
      "US",
      "LV",
      "VA",
      "AE",
      "QA"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'at'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "te",
    "answers": [
      "GT",
      "GB",
      "EH",
      "ME",
      "US",
      "US",
      "YT",
      "LI",
      "LI",
      "AE",
      "AE"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'te'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nt",
    "answers": [
      "ME",
      "MF",
      "SH",
      "CF",
      "KN",
      "LC",
      "VC",
      "VC",
      "AG",
      "AQ",
      "AR"
    ],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nt'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "so",
    "answers": ["BF", "GS", "GS", "ZA", "SB", "SO", "XK", "SS", "KR", "LS"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'so'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ga",
    "answers": ["BG", "GA", "GM", "HU", "PT", "MG", "UG", "SN", "SG", "TO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ga'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ea",
    "answers": ["TL", "GW", "GQ", "GN", "HM", "PG", "ER", "NZ", "KR", "KP"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ea'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "om",
    "answers": ["RO", "GB", "OM", "SB", "SO", "CO", "KM", "ST", "DO", "DM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'om'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "co",
    "answers": ["PR", "MA", "MC", "MX", "CI", "CO", "CG", "CD", "CR", "KM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'co'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "he",
    "answers": ["BA", "GS", "HM", "SH", "NL", "CG", "CD", "SC", "VC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'he'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ru",
    "answers": ["BN", "BI", "BY", "RU", "PE", "NR", "CY", "UY", "AW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ru'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ol",
    "answers": ["BO", "PF", "PL", "SB", "MD", "MN", "NF", "CO", "AO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ol'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ou",
    "answers": ["BV", "GS", "GS", "GP", "ZA", "SS", "KR", "DJ", "LU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ou'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "au",
    "answers": ["TK", "GW", "PW", "SA", "MU", "MR", "NR", "AU", "AT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'au'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ch",
    "answers": ["GS", "GF", "PF", "CN", "CL", "CZ", "SC", "LI", "TD"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ch'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "pa",
    "answers": ["JP", "PS", "PW", "PY", "PA", "PG", "PK", "ES", "NP"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'pa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "le",
    "answers": ["PS", "IM", "SH", "NC", "CL", "SL", "SC", "LB", "LS"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'le'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ki",
    "answers": ["BF", "TJ", "GB", "PK", "UZ", "KI", "KN", "SK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ki'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "bo",
    "answers": ["BA", "BO", "BV", "BW", "GA", "KH", "DJ", "LU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'bo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "vi",
    "answers": ["BA", "BO", "VN", "KN", "VG", "LV", "VC", "VI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'vi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "un",
    "answers": ["BN", "BI", "RE", "GB", "TN", "HU", "US", "AE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'un'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ha",
    "answers": ["BS", "GH", "HT", "EH", "MH", "TH", "TD", "AF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ha'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "si",
    "answers": ["RU", "TN", "PF", "MY", "FM", "SL", "SG", "ID"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'si'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "bi",
    "answers": ["RS", "GW", "GM", "ZM", "SA", "NA", "CO", "MZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'bi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ro",
    "answers": ["RO", "HR", "ME", "MA", "FM", "FO", "CM", "KM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ro'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "to",
    "answers": ["TK", "GQ", "PR", "EE", "ST", "TT", "TO", "TG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'to'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ir",
    "answers": ["IQ", "PN", "KI", "VG", "AE", "VI", "IR", "IE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ir'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "be",
    "answers": ["BE", "BM", "BJ", "BY", "BZ", "UZ", "LR"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'be'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "go",
    "answers": ["BA", "MN", "CG", "CD", "TT", "TG", "AO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'go'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ut",
    "answers": ["BT", "GS", "GS", "ZA", "SS", "KR", "DJ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ut'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "me",
    "answers": ["TM", "MX", "CM", "SR", "ST", "YE", "AM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'me'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ge",
    "answers": ["GS", "GE", "NE", "NG", "DE", "DZ", "AR"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ge'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rg",
    "answers": ["GS", "GE", "KG", "VG", "LU", "VI", "AR"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rg'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "va",
    "answers": ["SV", "SJ", "MD", "VU", "SK", "TV", "VA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'va'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "mb",
    "answers": ["GM", "ZM", "ZW", "CO", "KH", "LU", "MZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'mb'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "pu",
    "answers": ["PR", "PG", "CG", "CF", "CD", "CZ", "DO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'pu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ay",
    "answers": ["SJ", "PY", "MY", "NO", "KY", "UY", "YT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ay'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ub",
    "answers": ["CG", "CF", "CD", "CZ", "CU", "DO", "AW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ub'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "de",
    "answers": ["BD", "GP", "CD", "CV", "SE", "DK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'de'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "gi",
    "answers": ["BE", "GS", "GE", "GI", "VG", "VI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'gi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "as",
    "answers": ["BF", "BS", "TL", "HN", "MG", "CI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'as'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "os",
    "answers": ["BA", "BB", "XK", "CR", "KM", "LA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'os'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ze",
    "answers": ["BA", "BZ", "NZ", "CH", "CZ", "AZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ze'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "di",
    "answers": ["BI", "SA", "MV", "KH", "VC", "IN"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'di'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "wa",
    "answers": ["BW", "RW", "NO", "SZ", "KW", "TW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'wa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "us",
    "answers": ["BY", "RU", "MU", "CY", "AU", "AT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'us'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "tu",
    "answers": ["TM", "TN", "PT", "VU", "TV", "TR"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'tu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ce",
    "answers": ["GR", "MK", "FR", "CF", "VC", "IS"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ce'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ed",
    "answers": ["GB", "MK", "NC", "SE", "US", "AE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ed'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ib",
    "answers": ["GI", "NA", "KI", "DJ", "LR", "LY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ib'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ep",
    "answers": ["NP", "CG", "CF", "CD", "CZ", "DO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ep'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ov",
    "answers": ["BA", "MD", "XK", "SK", "SI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ov'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ud",
    "answers": ["BM", "SA", "SS", "SD", "AG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ud'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ve",
    "answers": ["BV", "VE", "MV", "CV", "SI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 've'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "il",
    "answers": ["BR", "PH", "CL", "SZ", "TH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'il'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "se",
    "answers": ["JE", "RS", "GG", "SN", "SC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'se'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ui",
    "answers": ["GW", "GQ", "GF", "GN", "PG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ui'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "em",
    "answers": ["GT", "CD", "YE", "LU", "AE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'em'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "gr",
    "answers": ["GR", "GD", "GL", "ME", "VC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'gr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "lo",
    "answers": ["GP", "SB", "CO", "SK", "SI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'lo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "fr",
    "answers": ["GF", "PF", "ZA", "FR", "CF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'fr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nc",
    "answers": ["GF", "PF", "FR", "ST", "VC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "tr",
    "answers": ["ER", "CF", "TT", "AU", "AT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'tr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "mi",
    "answers": ["FM", "NA", "DO", "DM", "AE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'mi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "no",
    "answers": ["NO", "NF", "KP", "SM", "LB"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'no'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "bl",
    "answers": ["CG", "CF", "CD", "CZ", "DO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'bl'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "bu",
    "answers": ["BF", "BG", "BI", "AG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'bu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rk",
    "answers": ["BF", "TM", "DK", "TR"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rk'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "eg",
    "answers": ["BA", "EG", "ME", "SN"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'eg'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rb",
    "answers": ["BB", "RS", "AG", "AZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rb'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "br",
    "answers": ["BN", "BR", "GI", "VG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'br'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ja",
    "answers": ["JM", "JP", "SJ", "AZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ja'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "et",
    "answers": ["BV", "VN", "ET", "NL"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'et'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sw",
    "answers": ["BW", "CH", "SZ", "SE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "az",
    "answers": ["BR", "SZ", "KZ", "AZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'az'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ey",
    "answers": ["JE", "GG", "SC", "TR"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ey'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ec",
    "answers": ["GR", "EC", "CZ", "LI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ec'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "pe",
    "answers": ["GP", "PE", "CV", "ST"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'pe'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ap",
    "answers": ["JP", "PG", "CV", "SG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ap'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ya",
    "answers": ["GY", "MM", "KE", "LY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ya'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ue",
    "answers": ["GG", "VE", "PR", "MZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ue'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ab",
    "answers": ["GA", "ZW", "SA", "AE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ab'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rd",
    "answers": ["JO", "HM", "SJ", "CV"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rd'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ko",
    "answers": ["HK", "XK", "KR", "KP"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ko'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rt",
    "answers": ["PR", "PT", "MF", "KP"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rt'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "po",
    "answers": ["PT", "PF", "PL", "SG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'po'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ag",
    "answers": ["PY", "MG", "NI", "TT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ag'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "hi",
    "answers": ["PH", "ET", "CN", "CL"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'hi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "za",
    "answers": ["ZM", "TZ", "KZ", "MZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'za'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sh",
    "answers": ["BD", "MH", "VG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sh'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "lg",
    "answers": ["BE", "BG", "DZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'lg'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "fa",
    "answers": ["BF", "FK", "FO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'fa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rm",
    "answers": ["BM", "DE", "AM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rm'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "iv",
    "answers": ["BO", "MV", "CI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'iv'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ah",
    "answers": ["BH", "BS", "EH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ah'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "hu",
    "answers": ["BT", "HU", "LT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'hu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ot",
    "answers": ["BW", "YT", "LS"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ot'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "oa",
    "answers": ["WS", "HR", "CI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'oa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "zi",
    "answers": ["BR", "ZW", "SZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'zi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ji",
    "answers": ["TJ", "FJ", "DJ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ji'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ke",
    "answers": ["TK", "KE", "TR"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ke'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "eo",
    "answers": ["GS", "GE", "SL"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'eo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "wi",
    "answers": ["GS", "MW", "CH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'wi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rn",
    "answers": ["GG", "PN", "EH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rn'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "cr",
    "answers": ["HR", "FM", "CD"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'cr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ho",
    "answers": ["HK", "HN", "LS"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ho'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ld",
    "answers": ["HM", "MD", "MV"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ld'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ug",
    "answers": ["PT", "UG", "UY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ug'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ew",
    "answers": ["PG", "NC", "NZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ew'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ak",
    "answers": ["PK", "SK", "KZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ak'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "pi",
    "answers": ["PH", "PN", "ET"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'pi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "we",
    "answers": ["EH", "ZW", "SE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'we'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "af",
    "answers": ["ZA", "CF", "AF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'af'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ie",
    "answers": ["VN", "SL", "LI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ie'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ac",
    "answers": ["MC", "MO", "MK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ac'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ao",
    "answers": ["MO", "ST", "LA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ao'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sl",
    "answers": ["IM", "SK", "SI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sl'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "of",
    "answers": ["IM", "CG", "CD"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'of'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ig",
    "answers": ["NE", "NG", "AG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ig'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "su",
    "answers": ["SS", "SR", "SD"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'su'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "lu",
    "answers": ["LC", "TV", "LU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'lu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "iu",
    "answers": ["BE", "MU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'iu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ei",
    "answers": ["BN", "LI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ei'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "uv",
    "answers": ["BV", "TV"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'uv'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ts",
    "answers": ["BW", "KN"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ts'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rs",
    "answers": ["JE", "MH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rs'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ss",
    "answers": ["RU", "GW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ss'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rw",
    "answers": ["RW", "NO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "im",
    "answers": ["TL", "ZW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'im'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "io",
    "answers": ["RE", "ET"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'io'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ee",
    "answers": ["GR", "GL"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ee'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "qu",
    "answers": ["GQ", "MZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'qu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ns",
    "answers": ["GG", "LI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ns'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nl",
    "answers": ["GL", "FI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nl'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "lt",
    "answers": ["GI", "MT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'lt'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "gh",
    "answers": ["GH", "AF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'gh'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ry",
    "answers": ["HU", "CI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ry'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "lb",
    "answers": ["SJ", "AL"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'lb'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ye",
    "answers": ["SJ", "YE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ye'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ly",
    "answers": ["PF", "IT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ly'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ip",
    "answers": ["PH", "ST"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ip'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "gy",
    "answers": ["EG", "KG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'gy'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "yp",
    "answers": ["EG", "CY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'yp'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "cu",
    "answers": ["EC", "CU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'cu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "oc",
    "answers": ["MA", "CD"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'oc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nm",
    "answers": ["MM", "DK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nm'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ll",
    "answers": ["MH", "SC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'll'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sr",
    "answers": ["IL", "LK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "fi",
    "answers": ["FI", "FJ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'fi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ij",
    "answers": ["FJ", "AZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ij'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "lk",
    "answers": ["FK", "NF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'lk'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rl",
    "answers": ["NL", "CH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rl'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "vo",
    "answers": ["XK", "CI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'vo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "pr",
    "answers": ["CY", "ST"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'pr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "yr",
    "answers": ["SY", "KG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'yr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ny",
    "answers": ["KE", "DE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ny'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "tt",
    "answers": ["KN", "YT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'tt'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ci",
    "answers": ["ST", "LC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ci'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rr",
    "answers": ["SL", "AD"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ka",
    "answers": ["KZ", "LK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ka'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "gl",
    "answers": ["BD"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'gl'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "um",
    "answers": ["BE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'um'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ul",
    "answers": ["BG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ul'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sn",
    "answers": ["BA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sn'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rz",
    "answers": ["BA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "mu",
    "answers": ["BM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'mu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "hr",
    "answers": ["BH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'hr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "bh",
    "answers": ["BT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'bh'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "je",
    "answers": ["JE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'je'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "iz",
    "answers": ["BZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'iz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "eu",
    "answers": ["RE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'eu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "km",
    "answers": ["TM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'km'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "aj",
    "answers": ["TJ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'aj'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ik",
    "answers": ["TJ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ik'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ok",
    "answers": ["TK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ok'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "a-",
    "answers": ["GW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'a-'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "-b",
    "answers": ["GW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring '-b'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "dw",
    "answers": ["GS"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'dw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "eq",
    "answers": ["GQ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'eq'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "up",
    "answers": ["GP"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'up'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "uy",
    "answers": ["GY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'uy'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "gd",
    "answers": ["GB"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'gd'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "lv",
    "answers": ["SV"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'lv'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "jo",
    "answers": ["JO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'jo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "du",
    "answers": ["HN"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'du'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "mc",
    "answers": ["HM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'mc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "cd",
    "answers": ["HM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'cd'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ez",
    "answers": ["VE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ez'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "zu",
    "answers": ["VE"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'zu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sv",
    "answers": ["SJ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sv'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "aq",
    "answers": ["IQ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'aq'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "yn",
    "answers": ["PF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'yn'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ph",
    "answers": ["PH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ph'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "pp",
    "answers": ["PH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'pp'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "tc",
    "answers": ["PN"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'tc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "pt",
    "answers": ["EG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'pt'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "tn",
    "answers": ["VN"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'tn'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "op",
    "answers": ["ET"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'op'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "bw",
    "answers": ["ZW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'bw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sp",
    "answers": ["ES"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sp'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sc",
    "answers": ["MG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "cc",
    "answers": ["MA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'cc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "uz",
    "answers": ["UZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'uz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "zb",
    "answers": ["UZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'zb'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ek",
    "answers": ["UZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ek'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "my",
    "answers": ["MM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'my'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "aw",
    "answers": ["MW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'aw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nz",
    "answers": ["TZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ys",
    "answers": ["MY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ys'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ex",
    "answers": ["MX"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ex'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "xi",
    "answers": ["MX"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'xi'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ae",
    "answers": ["IL"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ae'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "kl",
    "answers": ["FK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'kl'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "oe",
    "answers": ["FO"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'oe'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ds",
    "answers": ["NL"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ds'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nu",
    "answers": ["VU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nu'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rf",
    "answers": ["NF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rf'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "fo",
    "answers": ["NF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'fo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "tz",
    "answers": ["CH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'tz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "oo",
    "answers": ["CM"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'oo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "cz",
    "answers": ["CZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'cz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "cy",
    "answers": ["CY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'cy'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "sy",
    "answers": ["SY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'sy'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ky",
    "answers": ["KG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ky'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "yz",
    "answers": ["KG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'yz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "zs",
    "answers": ["KG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'zs'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "od",
    "answers": ["KH"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'od'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ev",
    "answers": ["KN"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ev'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ku",
    "answers": ["KW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ku'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "uw",
    "answers": ["KW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'uw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "yc",
    "answers": ["SC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'yc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "kh",
    "answers": ["KZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'kh'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "hs",
    "answers": ["KZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'hs'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ym",
    "answers": ["KY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ym'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "dj",
    "answers": ["DJ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'dj'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "yo",
    "answers": ["YT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'yo'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "eb",
    "answers": ["LB"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'eb'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "uc",
    "answers": ["LC"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'uc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "iw",
    "answers": ["TW"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'iw'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "id",
    "answers": ["TT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'id'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ob",
    "answers": ["TT"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ob'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "nk",
    "answers": ["LK"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'nk'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ht",
    "answers": ["LI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ht'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "tv",
    "answers": ["LV"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'tv'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ux",
    "answers": ["LU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ux'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "xe",
    "answers": ["LU"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'xe'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "og",
    "answers": ["TG"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'og'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "by",
    "answers": ["LY"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'by'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "fg",
    "answers": ["AF"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'fg'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "u.",
    "answers": ["VI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'u.'"
  },
  {
    "substring": ".s",
    "answers": ["VI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring '.s'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "s.",
    "answers": ["VI"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 's.'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "rc",
    "answers": ["AQ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'rc'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "ct",
    "answers": ["AQ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'ct'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "uk",
    "answers": ["UA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'uk'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "kr",
    "answers": ["UA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'kr'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "qa",
    "answers": ["QA"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'qa'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "oz",
    "answers": ["MZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'oz'"
  },
  {
    "substring": "iq",
    "answers": ["MZ"],
    "question": "Name contains the substring 'iq'"
  }
]
